<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Chloe Lain Bennett Site</title><link>https://chloelainb.github.io/blog/</link><description>Recent content on Chloe Lain Bennett Site</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chloelainb.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Build a Bears Video adventure</title><link>https://chloelainb.github.io/blog/p/build-a-bears-video-adventure/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chloelainb.github.io/blog/p/build-a-bears-video-adventure/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://chloelainb.github.io/blog/p/build-a-bears-video-adventure/picture.jpeg" alt="Featured image of post Build a Bears Video adventure" />&lt;p>This is my first stop motion movie that i did on my tablet. Its about two B-A-Bs [wich stands for build a bears]and one of them is waiting for they&amp;rsquo;re friend and they&amp;rsquo;re BFF comes so they had a little ride around but then comes this toy and they chase it until it just dissapears. To me this is around a an 9.5/10 it is good but not perfect.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="b-a-b-video">B-A-B Video
&lt;/h2>&lt;video controls width="100%">
&lt;source src="My_Stop_Motion_Movie.mp4" type="video/mp4">
Your browser does not support the video tag.
&lt;/video></description></item><item><title>Build a bears adventures (part 1)</title><link>https://chloelainb.github.io/blog/p/build-a-bears-adventures-part-1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chloelainb.github.io/blog/p/build-a-bears-adventures-part-1/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://chloelainb.github.io/blog/p/build-a-bears-adventures-part-1/picture.jpeg" alt="Featured image of post Build a bears adventures (part 1)" />&lt;h2 id="chapter-1">Chapter 1
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>Once there were two build a bears called Rosie the bunny and Cutie the cat ,they lived in build a bear land. One day they were both going to school and it was sports day. Luckily they were on the same team. They had to do jumping / sprinting and guess what?  Their team won! So they got to go to Nice in France.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="chapter-2">Chapter 2
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>The next day rosie and cutie were packing up so they did not have to do it on  the day,which was tomorrow. When it was dinner time they had a french friend called Aimee come to their house to cook them french food and to teach them some french words like:Hello, thank you and are there any sharks in the sea here.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="chapter-3">Chapter 3
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>In the morning they both had a bath and got dressed. Rosie got dressed  in her pumpkin dungarees. Cutie got dressed in her skirt and &amp;ldquo;I love Nice t-shirt&amp;rdquo;. After that they both got their suitcases and set off. They left at 6:00Am.They both had to get a taxi to London bridge station to get a train to Gatwick Airport so they then  got on the train and went to gatwick.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="chapter-4">Chapter 4
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>After quickly going through security they found out that the plane was delayed because of a storm. So they had to wait an extra hour for the flight. Cutie was happy because she didn&amp;rsquo;t want to fly in the rain.  After an hour the storm has passed and there sunny spells so cutie was feeling  relaxed.They both boarded the plane and sat down in their seats which were 54 and 53. They got some snacks to eat and put their pjs on and fell asleep.
THE END UNTIL PART 2 WICH IS COMING SOON!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Wrote by Chloe Lain Bennett     
I hope you liked my story. Thank you for reading&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Peacock and the Tiger</title><link>https://chloelainb.github.io/blog/p/peacock-and-the-tiger/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chloelainb.github.io/blog/p/peacock-and-the-tiger/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://chloelainb.github.io/blog/p/peacock-and-the-tiger/picture.jpeg" alt="Featured image of post Peacock and the Tiger" />&lt;h2 id="chapter-1">Chapter 1
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>Once there were two animals called Leon the tiger and Pepa the peacock. They were very close friends. They lived in a zoo. One day they were playing a game and loads of people came to them and looked at them. Leon and Pepa were both hearing “ooowww they are playing i have never seen a peacock and a tiger play, normally the tiger eats the peacock heehee”. Leon and Pepa were saying “Why are you looking at us weird people? OK let&amp;rsquo;s do a cute pose, maybe Tiger Swift will see us on TikTok you never know!”. At the end of the day when all the people left and they were playing before dinner they were just speaking about how weird that was because every single day they do that and none of the people were so “ooowww they are so cute” they had never done that so as soon as they called “dinner time” they quickly ran to the table for dinner. After dinner they had one more play time and then about 30 mins later they said “bed time!” so they quickly ran to bed.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="chapter-2">Chapter 2
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>The next day Pepa and Leon were playing in their cages. This time people looked at the Koala Narla and the people said the same thing &amp;ldquo;oooowwww that Koala is so cute&amp;rdquo;. Narla is one of the shyest animals in the zoo because recently she had a new sister called Skylar and her mum has to look after her so she doesn&amp;rsquo;t see her that much. Pepa looked over to the opposite side of Narlas cage and Pepa said &amp;ldquo;look at Piper the hippo, she never ever gets attention and there are loads of people looking at her now&amp;rdquo;. They all looked and spoke about her and said &amp;ldquo;poooooooyyyyyy that is stinky but look how good that hippo is diving into that mud&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="chapter-3">Chapter 3
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>The next day Pepa, Leon, Narla and Piper heard that they were going on school trips because they are so popular now, so they get to go on one every sunday. When they were getting into their paires to get on to the plane pepa and Leon agreed that they are going to have to have some rules about being BFFs and being kind to everyone! The rules were:&lt;/p>
&lt;p>1.They were kind and sat next to each other
2.they helped each other
3.DO ALL OF THESE THINGS&lt;/p>
&lt;p>When they got off the plane, they had a new teacher called Miss Bamboo who was a giant panda, they learned animal coding in the morning and at lunch time Miss Bamboo ate bamboo, Narla had some leaves from the garden, Leon had some meat, Pepa had bird seeds and Piper had a mud cake, they all ate at the same table. After lunch they had a writing class and were told to write about all the fun things they did that day. At the end of the day there was an argument between all the classmates because none of them could agree on what game to play in free time and it turned it into a nightmare when they did play a game because there were pairs and no one wanted to pair up! Because Pepa and Leon had a fight, Pepa was with Piper and Leon was with Narla. Leon rushed to the bathroom to cry because she never thought that Pepa would be so mean and forget their rules. On the way home Pepa sat with Piper and made Leon even more sad. Narla was trying to be kind to Leon but he didn&amp;rsquo;t really care as he was so upset with Pepa.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The end&lt;/p>
&lt;p>There will be other storys very soon.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>If you want you can visit: &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.londonzoo.org/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>London Zoo&lt;/a>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Music Theory Grade 1</title><link>https://chloelainb.github.io/blog/p/music-theory-grade-1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chloelainb.github.io/blog/p/music-theory-grade-1/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://chloelainb.github.io/blog/p/music-theory-grade-1/picture.jpeg" alt="Featured image of post Music Theory Grade 1" />&lt;p>Today I found out I passed my music theory grade 1 exam! Im going to try and pass my Piano Grade 1 later this year!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Archives</title><link>https://chloelainb.github.io/blog/archives/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chloelainb.github.io/blog/archives/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Links</title><link>https://chloelainb.github.io/blog/links/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chloelainb.github.io/blog/links/</guid><description>&lt;p>Here are a few of my favourite things!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Search</title><link>https://chloelainb.github.io/blog/search/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chloelainb.github.io/blog/search/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>